So, I'm going to have to express this properly.
So, this is going to be on my work.
What if my people work?
Is that?
So, we're going to have to express this properly.
I'm going to have to express this properly.
Sorry about those things.
So, we're going to have things taken between the two.
We're going to have the enseagues pass.
It's going to be a module from the ability to take the training.
So, we're going to have to try a quadcopter.
But it's like a dronecopter.
So, for landing, up and down, we'll just get to it.
So, enseagues, the gods, ends in November.
Espa stera.
I for India, Gisbergot, and I for India, I for India, is a human rights protocol.
It gives you food, water, and shelter.
We've got enseagues robots, human rights robots.
What enseagues is a drone.
So, enseagues is a drone aircraft for humanitarian aid.
For humanitarian aid.
So, this is a drone that African Eddowerta is an aircraft to carry food, water.
And shelter, food, water, and shelter for food and water.
Medical supplies, medication treatment, you know, for the kind of civil class,
the kind of worst kind of environment.
It is not a toy.
It is never a toy.
It is never a weapon.
And it's never a weapon.
And it's never a problem.
It's never a problem.
You know, these are the three closets of his thinking.
It's like, what is it down back?
Because he might feel cold, you know.
You know, it's never problematic.
It's never a toy.
And it's never a weapon.
And I'm trying to draw the diagrams today to suppress,
and discover, in kind of almost tense.
I'm just trying to throw this by the way.
But I want to explain.
Problem.
The never a toy is an aesthetic store.
It's a tri-lateral SDK.
That means the street SDK means they are three, a constitutional education.
So the first SDK is called never a toy.
And this is for human in the loop.
Human in the loop.
Human in the loop is never a problem.
Never a problem.
Human out of the loop.
Human out of the loop is the process of the operation.
Human out of the loop is never a weapon.
Human.
So you got to get human in the loop.
So you get human on the loop.
That's never a problem.
Human in the loop.
No, no, human in the loop.
Human in the loop is never a problem.
Human out of the loop.
Never a weapon.
And human on the loop is never a toy.
That means you can find a model for a case of your physics.
This is a spring physics or paint that elastic in a paint that can,
that can, that can, that can echo chamber, which means you can use twice.
You can use twice because you receive by a place in twice.
And this is a humer to us call.
This is basically bound to the ontological Bayesian intelligence infrastructure,
intelligence, OVI AI architecture, and infrastructure infrastructure,
and infrastructure infrastructure systems using top-down and bottom-up reasoning.
Top-down reasoning or what I call imperative reasoning
or bottom-up reasoning, what I call declative reasoning.
So without further ado, logistic
drawing. So here's my, my, my, my, my, my, um,
if you don't start drawing.
So I'm going to try to get in this break here.
So what I'm going to use is my protector here.
Put it here.
I'm going to do a turbine first.
So the turbines will be here.
So, uh, four centimeters.
Uh, here.
So the piston, the turbine's, um, left,
how, how the drone gets lit.
It won't have some two lift molds, two lift molds.
Let me draw the vertical mode.
So I'm not going to go right here.
So I've got a little wing here.
This is the center of my architecture here.
The properties goes to the center here.
And it's not a center, but the way I know that.
This is the 15, 15 kilo.
It's equal to five, 15 plus five.
It is 15 plus five.
It's 20, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20 centimeters.
It was five is 20.
The system is all to occur in teams.
So I'll do one by 15.
In team.
Oh, no, kind.
Only two here.
Okay.
I don't know.
You can.
Give it a half track.
You can have a stone coat here.
Don't go here.
I'm going to show the business line.
Not good.
I'm not going to store it here.
Okay.
Sorry.
I'm just a little bit of a thing.
What's the last?
Four.
I'll just add.
Two.
Four.
So.
For the day.
I was doing a couple of other gems.
We're going to act on the show.
Yeah.
Basically,
have a city down.
No truck up there.
Just a couple team.
Yeah.
We'll see you here.
Yeah, I don't know what the change is going to be.
At this point, we'll see it needs to be halfway.
Uh,
July and 11.
One and one is the turn.
One and one is the level of 19.
19 will be the turn.
And the turn of 1 will be the turn.
And it's fixed.
One.
We'll just forget about that.
And then we'll swap down.
So we're going to have a top down.
And the bridge here.
So this is a drone.
This sometimes you have the wings up here.
I'm doing the wing of the joint.
And this happens when you do look like stuff.
Do you know if you do it with the click?
If you have a three drone, but it's a four.
So this is a four with the drone.
So basically the drone going to be a four in one.
We're going to have the.
Four wings.
Four blades for four.
So that's.
So we're going to have four propellers for propellants.
Four propellers to prepare to an op-opt.
I'm going to have four.
I'm going to have.
Let's make it.
Five.
No, I'm always.
I'm.
Oh, yeah, four.
I'm going to have this here.
We're going to do this number.
So this is basically.
But I hear.
This is the second I care.
Nine nights.
This is the chart.
I was just down to the port.
I'm going to have a two.
This is 14 14.
14 14.
I'm going to have a.
Four zero zero.
I can have a couple of.
I can have something related here.
It's basically being.
You can have one, two, three.
One.
Try to do that way.
The one white construct.
One.
I'm going to have one.
You have a little money.
You're not a vertical tune line.
Or tune line.
You're not out here.
I'm not.
I'm not being able to.
Two.
Five.
Well, basically, it's going to be.
You're going to.
I'm going to have a.
The ring show.
Yes.
So, once the two are equal.
I don't know.
This is going to use one more.
It's five centimeters long.
No.
Let's make it to.
So, basically, this one looks like the two and half of the same as the log.
So, basically, you're going to have three wings and three wings are going to be like a four-wheel.
You're going to have three wings, as pain as four wings.
And then you try to cut some.
And I'm going to try to do, you're going to have one artificial wing.
One's to do, and you know, basically, it goes to have a kind of take-off procedure.
So, let me start designing properly, you know, I brought my human rights.
So, you're going to have three main wings.
And these three wings are acting like one big one, because I'm winning the concept of the air.
I'll set the altitude.
Obviously, if I go.
Extending each other here.
Or each of them is here.
Extending this is here.
So, we're going to do.
Three centimeters here.
No, no double this one.
Each of them is here.
Yes, this one is not the origin.
It will be here.
Yeah.
And I will do this one.
This will be a special set of angles.
This will make it.
So, if I go to the potential cost.
This 14.
I'm going to 14.
So, this needs to be in the same thing.
Angle of 14.
Angle of this here.
It was too sensitive, it was too big.
Here.
And this is the distance difference.
I'll take a look at the other one.
I'm going to have a tripod today.
They're going to have wings of ground on three centimeters.
So, this is too hollow.
I'm going to have a compass.
I don't know what to do.
I'm going to do this one.
Three centimeters.
This is the way.
Oh, three by the school.
I'm going to do three centimeters.
I mean, they're not moving really.
I'm going to do it even.
I don't know whether they even normally do break two centimeters.
No, it cannot be even.
That's the kind of logical mistake we're going to do.
I'm going to have.
That's the thing.
Three.
I don't think they're quite swimming.
I'm going to do it.
No, I should not work.
I'm going to do it here.
This is where I'm going to do it.
This is a long trip.
This is where the chance will be going to happen soon.
Although, this will get three by three.
I didn't expect it to matter what.
I think that's basically the job to show.
Basically, you're going to have three wings.
No, I can't do this.
This is a nice little breeze.
I have to go to the list.
I can't do this.
This is the peaceful being.
Let's take a look at the center here.
Since that's here, you have to turn.
I think you're going to have down here.
Don't you?
I'm going to turn.
Please, I'm going to turn.
This is basically an arc of...
I don't know.
Basically, this is the...
I'm going to turn.
This is the here.
This is the inside.
This is the one that's in the ring.
This is the green in the third.
It's all the way.
This is the third.
I'm going to turn.